W. C. Ives
Marist Archives and Special Collections
W. C. Ives
2.1.2.4.16
Marist College
MMM
MMM
MMM
  Box 1383
- W. C. Ives, 2.1.2.4.16
  - Petrified forest, circa 1900-1920; 14; 3x4 color (Box 1383)
  - Petrified forest, circa 1900-1920; 15; 3x4 color (Box 1383)
  - Petrified forest, circa 1900-1920; 16; 3x4 color (Box 1383)
  - Canyon, circa 1900-1920; 17; 3x4 color (Box 1383)
  - Canyon, circa 1900-1920; 18; 3x4 color (Box 1383)
  - Landscape, trees and lake, circa 1900-1920; 19; 3x4 color (Box 1383)
  - Landscape, trees and lake, circa 1900-1920; 20; 3x4 color (Box 1383)
  - View of mountain, circa 1900-1920; 21; 3x4 color (Box 1383)
  - View of mountain, circa 1900-1920; 22; 3x4 color (Box 1383)
  - View of mountain, man in foreground, circa 1900-1920; 23; 3x4 color (Box 1383)